gfxartist.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy statement - GFXartist.com - Served over 20,000,000 artworks

**Collection of your Personal Information**

GFXartist.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, telephone number, demographic information, and information that is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. 

GFXartist.com does not associate sensitive data, such as your race, religion, or political affiliations, with personally identifiable information. GFXartist.com takes precautions to segregate any sensitive data you may provide on GFXartist.com and services that reference your race, religion, sexual orientation, ethnicity or political affiliations. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through GFXartist.com public online forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: GFXartist.com does not read any of your private online communications. All messages and communication through GFXartist.com are completely confidential. 

There is also information about your connection and software on your computer. that is automatically collected by GFXartist.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by GFXartist.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of GFXartist.com. 

**Use of your Personal Information**

GFXartist.com does not sell, rent or lease its member lists to third parties. GFXartist.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, GFXartist.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to GFXartist.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

GFXartist.com keeps track of the pages our visitors visit within GFXartist.com, in order to determine what pages on GFXartist.com are the most popular. This data is used to get a better idea of the interests of our visitors. 

**Use of Cookies**

GFXartist.com uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize GFXartist.com pages, or register with GFXartist.com, a cookie helps GFXartist.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to GFXartist.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the GFXartist.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of GFXartist.com. 

**Use of Third Party Ad Networks**

The majority of the online banner advertisements you see GFXartist.com are displayed by GFXartist.com. 

In addition, GFXartist.com also allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on GFXartist.com. To do this, ad networks place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. GFXartist.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. 

If you want to prevent third-party companies from sending and reading cookies on your computer, you will need to visit each ad network's Web site individually and request that you be removed from its system.

GFXartist.com has currently advertising partnerships with:  
[Burstmedia.com](http://www.burstmedia.com/) and [Valueclick.com](http://www.valueclick.com/)

**Control your Personal Information**

GFXartist.com offers its members choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go to your personal profile to proactively make choices about the use and sharing of your personal information. You may choose not to publicly expose your real name and or email address. 

In addition, you may visit your profile to view, edit or delete your personal information from the GFXartist.com database. 

In both cases described above, you will be asked to make your requests while logged into your GFXartist.com member account, so that GFXartist.com can associate your preferences with a particular account. This security safeguard prevents someone else from making choices about the usage and control of your personal information.

**Security of your Personal Information**

GFXartist.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. GFXartist.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

Changes to this Statement GFXartist.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect our and your feedback. When GFXartist.com posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of GFXartist.com. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how GFXartist.com will use your personally identifiable information, GFXartist.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. GFXartist.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how GFXartist.com is protecting your information. 

**Contact Information**

GFXartist.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that GFXartist.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact GFXartist.com by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail. 

GFXartist.com  
Schieland 11  
1274 LB, Huizen  
Tel. +31 355237355  
Fax. +31355237544  
The Netherlands

Click here to send [e-mail](http://www.gfxartist.com/support@gfxartist.com).
